<rst>
	<header>
		<relations>
			<rel name="antithesis" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="background" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="cause" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="circumstance" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="concession" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="condition" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="contrast" type="multinuc"/>
			<rel name="elaboration" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="evaluation" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="evidence" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="joint" type="multinuc"/>
			<rel name="justify" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="motivation" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="preparation" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="purpose" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="restatement" type="multinuc"/>
			<rel name="restatement" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="result" type="rst"/>
			<rel name="sequence" type="multinuc"/>
			<rel name="solutionhood" type="rst"/>
		</relations>
	</header>
	<body>
		<segment id="1" >But the -- if I describe the process, I think it will be clear.</segment>
		<segment id="2" parent="3" relname="circumstance">When the government responds to needs in the defense department, it does so through Congress, through increased spending.</segment>
		<segment id="3" >That spending ends up into an NDAA appropriation.</segment>
		<segment id="4" parent="5" relname="preparation">That appropriation is -- flows into the DoD, where they conceptualize things that they need.</segment>
		<segment id="5" parent="6" relname="elaboration">They structure them in contracts.</segment>
		<segment id="6" >They have competitions.</segment>
		<segment id="7" parent="8" relname="result">The contractor or -- is awarded a victory, and then the need for space manifests in our portfolio.</segment>
		<segment id="8" >So it's generally at least 12 in 18 to 24 months after the increase in the defense spending act that will realize the benefit in leasing, which is why my comments convey confidence in demand through 2024.</segment>
		<segment id="9" >Operator Our next question comes from Brian Spahn of Evercore ISI.</segment>
		<segment id="10" parent="11" relname="circumstance">Brian Spahn Steve, so you talked about 4% annual compounding FFO growth beginning in 2023.</segment>
		<segment id="11" parent="12" relname="elaboration">Could you maybe just walk us through the components of that?</segment>
		<segment id="12" parent="13" relname="circumstance">And what you're assuming in terms of Regional Office -- regional asset sales there?</segment>
		<segment id="13" >To what degree would these forecasts be affected by a recession?</segment>
		<segment id="14" parent="15" relname="concession">Steve Budorick Well, so that's a great question.</segment>
		<segment id="15" parent="16" relname="evaluation">I don't want to get into specific components and have this be misconstrued in some sort of guidance.</segment>
		<segment id="16" parent="21" relname="span">What I can say is management has conveying strong confidence in the company's position to generate that growth.</segment>
		<segment id="17" parent="21" relname="preparation">And that confidence really comes from our 5-year modeling process that we completed at the beginning of year.</segment>
		<segment id="18" parent="17" relname="evaluation">And our most recent modeling process dealt with the '22 to '26 period, and it was robust.</segment>
		<segment id="19" parent="18" relname="condition">We ran 10 different scenarios and then stress those scenarios.</segment>
		<segment id="20" parent="19" relname="condition">So to give you an example, we had 4 different capital recycling alternatives.</segment>
		<group id="21" type="span" />
	</body>
</rst>
